internetseer.com 2016-11-19

# Internetseer - Website Monitoring and Web Server Monitoring Service

**Summary**

InternetSeer values and respects the privacy of the Company's Subscribers to our free and fee-based services. Because we gather certain types of information about our Subscribers we want to help you understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. These privacy practices apply to the InternetSeer Web site that you were viewing when you clicked through to this policy, which is operated by InternetSeer, its partners or affiliates. These privacy practices apply only to online transactions, activity and to all email communications. All credit card transactions are processed through secure connections. InternetSeer uses proven technologies that improve the privacy of our Subscribers' information. InternetSeer will not sell your email address to anyone without your express permission and we control all e-mail delivery to assure your privacy. When we do share information with our partners and advertisers, it is in aggregate form, and does not identify you personally. InternetSeer does not collect or use any information about you except for the information that you provide or is publicly available, and this information is used solely to make the services provided more relevant to your interests. Under no circumstances is your e-mail address ever shared with advertisers. InternetSeer provides both free and fee-based services. The free services are supported by our advertisers and sponsors. By becoming an InternetSeer Subscriber, you agree to the InternetSeer Services Agreement Terms and Conditions. This includes your agreement to receive communications including monitoring alerts, weekly reports, announcements, updates and other carefully screened special offers and promotions. This is essential to maintaining certain services free to our subscribers. If you do not wish to view and receive such communications, you may cancel your account at the My InternetSeer section of our Web site or by following the instructions at the end of the email you receive from InternetSeer. If you do this, your account will automatically be terminated and you will receive no further service or contact from InternetSeer. 

**1\. What Personally Identifiable Information Does InternetSeer Collect?**

InternetSeer's primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with the best and most useful content and services. Because InternetSeer derives its revenue mainly from advertising and fee-based services, collecting information is essential to keeping certain of our services free. It is also necessary to assure the relevancy of this advertising to our Subscribers. InternetSeer collects personally identifiable information when a Subscriber provides it to us, such as when you subscribe to our services, complete the Subscriber survey, update your Subscriber profile on our Web site, use certain products or services, respond to our weekly email reports and monitoring alerts, and when you visit the InternetSeer Web site. Several of the services that we offer may require registration as a condition of use. InternetSeer may also receive information about you from other sources and add it to the information you have provided to us. 

**2\. What Anonymous Information Does InternetSeer Collect?**

**Cookies**

Your Internet browser has a feature called "cookies" which stores small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to our site. However, cookies tell us nothing about who you are unless you specifically give us personally identifiable information. You do not need to have cookies turned on to visit the InternetSeer site, although active participation in certain areas of our site may require cookies. In addition, you may elect not to allow cookies to be collected by selecting certain options on your browser. 

**Visitor Activities**

To track general Subscriber traffic patterns, we use electronic images known as single-pixel GIFs, transparent GIFs, or clear gifs. InternetSeer also automatically receives and records information from our servers and from your browser including your IP address, the time, and information about the page you requested. In order to determine which features Subscribers find most useful, we use tracking technologies in a variety of ways, including: keeping count of return visits to our site or our advertisers' or partners' sites and accumulating and reporting anonymous, aggregate (data collected in mass), statistical information on Web site and advertisement usage. 

**Third-Party Advertisement Servers**

Some of our advertisers use third-party companies to serve their advertisements on our site and, in some cases, in our HTML-formatted email reports. Often, these third-party advertising companies employ cookie and visitor activity technologies to measure advertisement effectiveness. We do not give any personally identifiable information to them as part of this relationship. Use of their tracking technology is subject to their own privacy policies. If you would like more information about the privacy policies of the third-party advertising providers including information on how to opt out of their tracking methods, check their respective sites or send request to [**privacy@internetseer.com**](mailto:privacy@internetseer.com&subject=Privacy%20Request%20from%20InternetSeer%20website.). 

**3\. How Does InternetSeer Use The Subscriber Information Gathered?**

InternetSeer uses the information we gather for the following purposes: 

  * To notify you with our monitoring alerts and weekly reports related to the availability of your Web site. 
  * To enhance the Subscriber experience we use tracking information to determine how well each page performs overall based on aggregate Subscriber demographics and traffic patterns to those pages. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. 
  * To fulfill your requests for certain products and services, such as sending out electronic newsletters and enabling Subscribers to participate in polls and contests. 
  * To customize the promotions, advertising and content you see, which helps keep certain of our services free to Subscribers. This allows our sponsors and advertisers to market their products and services more effectively, and allows our Subscribers to receive promotions and advertisements that are pertinent to their interests and needs. This, in turn, helps keep certain of our services free to Subscribers. 
  * To send Subscribers information about InternetSeer as well as announcements, updates and other carefully screened special offers and promotions from InternetSeer and our partners. Subscribers may expect to receive no more than four special offers or promotions by email per month. 

**4\. How Does InternetSeer Share The Information?**

**Personally Identifiable Information**

The following paragraphs describe how the Company currently uses personally identifiable information, but the Company may change or broaden its use at any time as permitted by law. InternetSeer will not sell your email address to anyone without your express permission and we control all email delivery to assure your privacy. InternetSeer will make your personally identifiable information available to other companies, individuals or other third parties under certain situations, such as when we have your consent to share the information, we have engaged companies to work with or on behalf of InternetSeer to provide a product or service that you have requested, and when you use co-branded services. When you use a co-branded service within our network, you grant us permission to pass your registration information back to that service partner. Their use of your information is subject to their applicable privacy policies. We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or we believe that your actions violate applicable laws, InternetSeer's Terms of Use or any usage guidelines for specific products or services, or threaten the rights, property or safety of InternetSeer, our Subscribers, or others. 

**Compliance with Laws and Communications with Legal Authorities**

InternetSeer responds to subpoenas, court orders and legal requests from authorities. We may contact the authorities if we believe that your actions violate applicable laws, InternetSeer's Services Agreement Terms and Conditions, usage guidelines for specific products or services, threaten the rights, property or safety of InternetSeer, our Subscribers, or others. 

**Aggregate Information**

InternetSeer aggregates personally identifiable information and discloses such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for marketing, promotional and other purposes. 

**Internet Business Services**

Internet Business Services are on-line fee-based services provided by divisions of InternetSeer and third party strategic partners. As an added benefit of subscribing to the InternetSeer remote Web site monitoring service, InternetSeer offers reasonably priced Internet Business Services targeted to the small business market. Subscribers who use our Internet Business Services may enter account data for private label or third-party services. This information is necessarily passed on to those third parties when their ordering system is accessed. 

**Business Transfers**

InternetSeer is always seeking to improve our Web site, Web site monitoring features and Internet Business Services. In accomplishing these objectives, we may buy or sell a company, or one or more of the companies in our corporate family may merge with or be acquired by another company. In the event of a merger, consolidation, or sale or transfer of all or substantially all of the assets or business of the company by, with, or into another company (a "Successor"), one of the assets which would generally be transferred is the information we collect from our customers, subscribers, and users. However, the use of this information by any Successor would still be governed by the terms of this Privacy Policy, as amended from time to time, including any amendment after such transaction, and you will continue to have the right to opt-out of sharing your information with third parties. A Successor to our business is not considered to be a third party for these purposes. 

**5\. What Are Your Options?**

Subscribers provide Subscriber data requested by our activation process. The InternetSeer Services Agreement Terms and Conditions requires Subscribers to receive email communications including monitoring alerts, weekly reports, announcements, updates and other carefully screened special offers and promotions. This is essential to maintaining certain services free to our subscribers. If you do not wish to view and receive such communications, you may cancel your account at the My InternetSeer section of our web site or by following the instructions at the end of the email you receive from InternetSeer or our marketing partners. If you do this, your account will automatically be terminated and you will receive no further service or contact from InternetSeer. 

**6\. How Can You Update Your Personally Identifiable Information?**

You can correct or change the information collected during activation for any service. The instructions for doing this can be found in the My InternetSeer area of our Web site. Subscribers may change this information at any time and as often as necessary. Subscribers who are experiencing problems or who have questions about how our services work can contact InternetSeer using the email address at the bottom of this page. 

**7\. How Will You Know If The Privacy Policy Is Changed?**

By visiting the InternetSeer Web site, becoming a Subscriber, or using the free or fee-based services, you hereby provide your consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy, and are aware that our policy may change over time. Specifically, this Privacy Policy may be updated to reflect new features, services and options, and any changes on the use of personal information. Continued use of the InternetSeer Web site and its services will indicate that you agree with any changes. Any modifications to our privacy practices will be reflected within this area of our Web site. 

**8\. Privacy of Children**

Our Web site is not directed to children. We do not knowingly permit registration by and will not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from, anyone under 13 years of age. 

**Questions, Comments**

Questions regarding this privacy statement, or any other aspects of our Web site or email communication, should be sent via email to our corporate offices at: [**privacy@InternetSeer.com**](mailto:privacy@InternetSeer.com)

You may also write to us at: 

ATTN: Customer Service  
381 Brinton Lake Road  
Thornton, PA 19373
